<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>NightNoon</title>
    <link>https://nightnoon.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NightNoon</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://nightnoon.org/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://nightnoon.org/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 09:02:59 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nightnoon.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Technical Utility Bookmarks</title>
      <link>https://nightnoon.org/posts/tech-bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 09:02:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nightnoon.org/posts/tech-bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>Technical Utility Bookmarks These are some utility pages I keep bookmarked as technical references when developing. I&amp;rsquo;m going to treat this like an Awesome List, so it will be a work in progress as I add more bookmarks.
Crontab Guru The crontab guru takes the guesswork out of crontab schedules: crontab guru. Paste in an existing schedule you are debugging or check out the example page for suggestions that might be useful for a new schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boredjar</title>
      <link>https://nightnoon.org/posts/boredjar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 18:40:55 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nightnoon.org/posts/boredjar/</guid>
      <description>Bored Jar The bored jar is something my daughter and I made and is intended to address the complaining of children in a constructive way. My daughter is 6, but I think this idea works for kids 5-10. Very young kids love to play with the cards if they&amp;rsquo;re laminated too.
The best part about about jar is that it is the first bored activity. Next time your kid is bored on a rainy day sit them down in front of this site and have them make the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Inception of This Blog</title>
      <link>https://nightnoon.org/posts/inception/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 10:39:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nightnoon.org/posts/inception/</guid>
      <description>Welcome, I am using this blog to explore my interests. Anything that excites me enough to keep me up into the wee hours tinkering is fare play for the blog. Hence the title NightNoon, as in &amp;ldquo;Should I go to bed? No! It&amp;rsquo;s barely night noon.&amp;rdquo;
The site is built using Hugo which will serve as the first topic to explore for the blog. I&amp;rsquo;m taking a page from Simon Willison who has suggested blogging in bite size chunks and starting with TIL posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
